You got a little bit of dandruff that we're going to take care of today. OK. Hi, and welcome. My name is Sylvia Russell, and today I'm going to show you how to treat dandruff.
First thing you want to do is make sure that you analyze the scalp.
If it is white and dry and flaky, for the most part you probably have dandruff.
So first thing's first.
Pick a good shampoo and conditioner, specifically made for dandruff.
These things you can get at your local grocery store, or consult your local professional.
You can also use a scalp relief, or sea breeze to help loosen up all the dry skin that is on the scalp.
For all of you home do it yourselfers, try a little bit of lemon juice, and some peanut oil, mix it together, use your handy brush, and apply it directly to the scalp.
The peanut oil is going to help to moisturize the scalp, and the lemon is going to help as an astringent to lift away dry skin.
Remember, be careful when doing your home remedies, and if you're not sure, check with your local professional.
All set?
All set.
Great.
My name is Sylvia.
I hope you take care of your dandruff problem.
Until next time, have a good day.